{"questions":[{"question":"What is the primary goal of software maintenance?","answers":[{"1":4},{"2":4},{"3":4},{"4":4}],"correct_ans":"2","diffculty":"2"},{"question":"What is a common challenge in software project management?","answers":[{"1":4},{"2":4},{"3":4},{"4":4}],"correct_ans":"2","diffculty":"2"},{"question":"Software engineering is an engineering discipline that is concerned with:","answers":[{"1":4},{"2":4},{"3":4},{"4":4}],"correct_ans":"4","diffculty":"1"},{"question":"Why did the software fail in 2005?","answers":[{"1":4},{"2":4},{"3":4},{"4":4}],"correct_ans":"4","diffculty":"2"},{"question":"What is a prototype?","answers":[{"1":4},{"2":4},{"3":4},{"4":4}],"correct_ans":"1","diffculty":"1"},{"question":"Which is a key principle of Agile software development?","answers":[{"1":4},{"2":4},{"3":4},{"4":4}],"correct_ans":"3","diffculty":"1"},{"question":"In software engineering, what is \u0027refactoring\u0027 primarily used for?","answers":[{"1":4},{"2":4},{"3":4},{"4":4}],"correct_ans":"2","diffculty":"2"},{"question":"What does \u0027scalability\u0027 refer to in software engineering?","answers":[{"1":4},{"2":4},{"3":4},{"4":4}],"correct_ans":"2","diffculty":"2"},{"question":"In a software development team, what is the role of a \u0027Scrum Master\u0027?","answers":[{"1":4},{"2":4},{"3":4},{"4":4}],"correct_ans":"3","diffculty":"2"},{"question":"What is \u0027continuous integration\u0027 in software development?","answers":[{"1":4},{"2":4},{"3":4},{"4":4}],"correct_ans":"2","diffculty":"2"},{"question":"Which of the following best describes \u0027pair programming\u0027?","answers":[{"1":4},{"2":4},{"3":4},{"4":4}],"correct_ans":"2","diffculty":"1"},{"question":"What is the main purpose of a \u0027code review\u0027?","answers":[{"1":4},{"2":4},{"3":4},{"4":4}],"correct_ans":"2","diffculty":"1"},{"question":"What is \u0027technical debt\u0027?","answers":[{"1":4},{"2":4},{"3":4},{"4":4}],"correct_ans":"4","diffculty":"2"},{"question":"Development Testing is  :","answers":[{"1":4},{"2":4},{"3":4},{"4":4}],"correct_ans":"1","diffculty":"3"},{"question":"Which of these are the activities of the software process","answers":[{"1":4},{"2":4},{"3":4},{"4":4}],"correct_ans":"4","diffculty":"3"},{"question":"What does a staff development program describe","answers":[{"1":4},{"2":4},{"3":4},{"4":4}],"correct_ans":"4","diffculty":"1"},{"question":"Sequence Diagram:","answers":[{"1":4},{"2":4},{"3":4},{"4":4}],"correct_ans":"2","diffculty":"2"},{"question":": Model Driven Engineering is (MDE)","answers":[{"1":4},{"2":4},{"3":4},{"4":4}],"correct_ans":"4","diffculty":"3"},{"question":"which diagram is a UML diagram?","answers":[{"1":4},{"2":4},{"3":4},{"4":4}],"correct_ans":"3","diffculty":"1"},{"question":"What is the primary purpose of defining requirements in software development?","answers":[{"1":4},{"2":4},{"3":4},{"4":4}],"correct_ans":"2","diffculty":"2"},{"question":"What are non-functional requirements in a software project?","answers":[{"1":4},{"2":4},{"3":4},{"4":4}],"correct_ans":"2","diffculty":"2"},{"question":"What is the role of ethnography in requirement analysis?","answers":[{"1":4},{"2":4},{"3":4},{"4":4}],"correct_ans":"2","diffculty":"3"},{"question":"Why are requirements in a software project often considered incomplete or inconsistent?","answers":[{"1":4},{"2":4},{"3":4},{"4":4}],"correct_ans":"2","diffculty":"2"},{"question":"What is the purpose of creating prototypes in the requirements analysis phase?","answers":[{"1":4},{"2":4},{"3":4},{"4":4}],"correct_ans":"2","diffculty":"2"},{"question":"What does Requirement Traceability refer to in software development?","answers":[{"1":4},{"2":4},{"3":4},{"4":4}],"correct_ans":"2","diffculty":"3"},{"question":"What are the main types of requirements in software engineering?","answers":[{"1":4},{"2":4},{"3":4},{"4":4}],"correct_ans":"1","diffculty":"1"},{"question":"How are \u0027user requirements\u0027 and \u0027system requirements\u0027 different?","answers":[{"1":4},{"2":4},{"3":4},{"4":4}],"correct_ans":"3","diffculty":"2"},{"question":"What challenges might arise in collecting and analyzing software requirements?","answers":[{"1":4},{"2":4},{"3":4},{"4":4}],"correct_ans":"1","diffculty":"2"},{"question":"Why is Agile methodology considered effective in managing changing requirements?","answers":[{"1":4},{"2":4},{"3":4},{"4":4}],"correct_ans":"3","diffculty":"2"}]}